A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, West Africa Program, RG 5 FA1766
Rockefeller Archive Center
- West Africa Program, 1953-1977, bulk 1957-1963; 1957-1963; 5; 12.4 Cubic Feet 30 boxes
  - Feasibilities Studies, 1959-1963; 3; 2 Cubic Feet
    - Nigeria - Report on the Feasibility of Establishing an Integrated Steel Mill in Nigeria, 1962 October (Box 28, Folder 224)
    - Nigeria, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 225)
      Investigation of the Feasibility of Establishing a Gravel Washing-Crushing-Grading Industry in Nigeria, January 1963.
      The Feasibility of a Core-Stock Veneer Mill in Eastern Nigeria, November 1963.